progressforamerica.org 2006-11-17

# Progress for America

To protect your privacy, Progress for America, Inc.(PFA) adheres to the following privacy and data protection principles:

**NOTICE**  
PFA may ask for information that personally identifies you (personal information) or allows us to contact you. Generally this information is requested when you join our organization or sign up for updates, newsletters, or other information published by PFA.  

**CHOICE AND CONSENT**  
We respect the purpose for which our site visitors give us information. We give users choice and consent over how their personal information is used, and remove names immediately upon request. 

**THIRD PARTY USE**  
PFA does not sell or rent our member or subscriber lists to third parties for any purpose. 

**ACCESS & UNSUBSCRIBE**  
PFA allows you to edit personal information you have already given us and/or unsubscribe to any email lists you have previously signed up for on our site.  We keep our subscription lists as clean as possible to prevent obsolete e-mails that may take unnecessary bandwidth. 

**SECURITY**  
PFA has taken strong measures to protect the security of your personal information and to ensure that your choices for its intended use are honored. We take strong precautions to protect your data from loss, misuse, unauthorized access or disclosure, alteration, or destruction. 

**COOKIES**  
"Cookies" are small files downloaded to your hard drive that enable your browser to save and recall information.  PFA uses cookies in a responsible manner to help our visitors quickly and easily navigate our site.  We do not collect or use this information from cookies to develop a profile about our members and other site visitors. 

**ENFORCEMENT**  
If you believe PFA has not adhered to the above principles, please notify us by email at [info@progressforamerica.org](mailto:info@progressforamerica.org), and we will do our best to determine and correct the problem promptly.   Please include the words "Privacy Policy" in the subject line. 

**NOTICE TO PARENTS**  
We want to help you guard your children's privacy. We encourage you to talk to your children about safe and responsible use of their Personal Information while using the Internet.
